https://www.techwyse.com/privacy-policy/

Cool Stuff! amazing ideas
Cool Stuff!
Privacy Policy
TechWyse is committed to protecting your privacy. This policy outlines our personal information handling practices for both online and offline data. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this policy.
When TechWyse collects any personal information VIA a corporate or sponsored website, we will express our need for the personal data at the point of collection. Personal information is any information that can be used to identify an individual, and may include, but is not limited to, name, e-mail address, postal or other physical address, title, occupation, and other information required to provide a service, deliver a product, or carry out a transaction you have requested. We will only use your personal information in the way we specified when it is collected. We will not subsequently change the way your personal information is used without your consent.
Unsubscribing
If you receive an e-mail from us, each e-mail includes instructions on how you can unsubscribe from that particular mailing.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell or rent your personal information to third-parties for marketing purposes unless you have granted us permission to do so.
We may respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process by disclosing your personal information and other related information, if necessary. We also may choose to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
We may collect and possibly share personal information and any other additional information available to us in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of TechWyse's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
While navigating TechWyse's web site you may be directed to content or functionality that is hosted by a third party supplier, not on TechWyse.com. This is typically done to host special events, such as contests. When information is collected on behalf of TechWyse exclusively, TechWyse's privacy policy will be referenced on the site and will govern how your information is used. For other, non-TechWyse sites, the site owner's privacy policy will be referenced. It is TechWyse's practice to require such suppliers to handle information in a manner consistent with TechWyse's privacy and security policies.
We will ask you for your opt-in consent to share your personal information with a third party for any other reason.
Security of your personal information
TechWyse is committed to protecting the personal information you share with us. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit.
We recommend you to take every precaution in protecting your personal information when you are on the Internet. For example, change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers when creating passwords, and make sure you use a secure browser.
Data retention
TechWyse will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or as required by applicable laws or regulations.
Third-Party Web Beacons
We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, click the request information button below.
CAN-SPAM and CASL Compliant
TechWyse is compliant with CAN-SPAM and CASL regulations in all email communication in order to ensure the protection of user data. All email communication to users is through opt-in consent, display the sender’s contact and business information, provide a visible unsubscribe link, and are always truthful.
TechWyse explicitly states a truthful subject line, email subject matter, URLs, and hyperlinks. We also include the street address and company name in all marketing and sales email communication by TechWyse or on behalf of clients.
In correspondence with regulations, it is our duty to ensure email lists and personal information are up-to-date.
GDPR Compliant
TechWyse is compliant with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) for email communication in and outside of the European Union as of May 25, 2018. This is to ensure the protection of user data of E.U. citizens by requiring user opt-in consent for email communication. Any user data that is stored is by pseudonymization or anonymization. Opt-in consent for email communication can be withdrawn at any time.
CONTACT US
Speak with sales
Our services are smooth and efficient. Call us today at
866.410.7090
Request a consultation
Get tips sent by email
Sign up for our updates
Socialize with us
TechWyse is always looking for passionate people.
Are you ready?
Cool Stuff!
© 2020 TechWyse Internet Marketing. All Rights Reserved.
Please wait...
